(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T09:07:03.712465",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
いくよー！
Here we go!
Dream☆Story
作詞・作編曲：キノシタ
[Song: Dream☆Story]
Music & Lyrics: Kinoshita
いくよ？
Ready?
ふっと忘れてしまいたくなる
Sometimes I suddenly want to forget
昨日のあの記憶のピース
Those pieces of yesterday's memories.
ねぇ無くなりはできそうもないけど
Hey, they're impossible to get rid of completely,
うまく繋げばまた続きへ
but if we connect them well, the story continues.
でも今は関係ないんだよ
But none of that matters right now!
そんなことも忘れちゃうような
Let's forget all about that
不思議な世界にアクセル全開で
and dive full throttle into this mysterious world,
飛び込もう It's show time!
It's show time!
でもでも急ぎっぱなしは禁物です
Still, rushing headlong is forbidden,
急がば回るって言うくらいじゃ
as the saying goes: "more haste, less speed."
だからたまにはゆっくり一休みしたら
So if we take a nice, slow break every now and then,
それじゃそうよ雨のリズムで
then let's go with that soothing rhythm.
止まらねぇぞ！
We won't stop!
飛んでけ FLY!
Fly away, FLY!
大きく息を吸ったら
Take a deep breath,
ボクらのストーリーが今溢れ出すよ
and now our story overflows.
もっともっと大きくね 最初が肝心なんです！
Make it bigger and bigger, the start is what counts!
はじめまして、こんにちは！せーの
Nice to meet you, hello! Ready, set,
ホロライブだよ！
We are Hololive!
もう一度 FLY! そら遠くまで届けドキドキで
Once more, FLY! Reaching far into the sky with a pounding heart.
奇想天外に彩っていく Dream☆Story
A wildly colorful Dream☆Story!
やっぱ1秒たりとも目を離して欲しいな
I want you to keep your eyes on me every single second.
瞬きもしてらんない
You won't even have time to blink!
あぁほらね 最高でしょ？ イエーイ！
Ah, see? Isn't it amazing? Yeah!
一歩進めばまた後ろへ
Take one step forward, then one step back,
見えない力が邪魔をしている
as an unseen force gets in the way.
ジャンプしたりできたらいいけれど
It would be great if we could just jump over it,
それも愛嬌、どうぞよろしく
but that's part of our charm, so please treat us well!
でも今は関係ないんだよ
But none of that matters right now,
心響くリズムを辿れば
if we follow the rhythm echoing in our hearts.
不思議な世界の続きのページで
On the next page of this mysterious world,
また出会えた Destiny
we met Destiny once again.
もしもし遅めのテンポもいいけど
Hello? A slower tempo is nice too,
今はそんな場合じゃないわけじゃない？
but isn't this really not the time for that?
だけど大丈夫、一息つけけたのならさ
Still, it's alright—if you've caught your breath,
いちにのさんの合図で (いちにのさん！)
on the count of one, two, three! (One, two, three!)
飛んでけ FLY!
Fly away, FLY!
大きな声で叫んだら
Shouting out with a loud voice,
ボクらのストーリーが今紡がれてく
our story is now being woven together.
もっともっと大きくね ボリュームはMAXで
Make it bigger and bigger, volume at MAX!
はじめまして、こんにちは！せーの ホロライブだよ！
Nice to meet you, hello! Ready, set, Hololive!
もう一度 FLY! そら遠くまで響けはちゃめちゃで
Once more, FLY! Echoing far into the sky, wildly and crazily,
摩訶不思議に煌めいたんだ Dream☆Story
sparkling mysteriously in our Dream☆Story.
やっぱ1秒たりとも体感していたいの
I want to experience every single second,
くらくらしちゃうくらい あぁだけど最高じゃない？
making me dizzy—ah, but isn't that the best?
ねぇねぇテンション 高まってアテンション
Hey hey, tension rising, attention!
ワクワク警報は鳴り止まない
The excitement alarm just won't stop ringing.
ねぇねぇテンション 高まってアテンション 誰も止められないわ！
Hey hey, tension rising, attention, nobody can stop us!
飛んでけ FLY!
Fly away, FLY!
大きく息を吸ったら
Take a deep breath,
ボクらのストーリーが今溢れ出すよ
and now our story overflows.
もっともっと大きくね 最初が肝心なんです！
Make it bigger and bigger, the start is what counts!
これからはさ、よろしくね！せーの
From now on too, please treat us well! Ready, set,
ホロライブだよ！
We are Hololive!
もう一度 FLY! そら遠くまで届けドキドキで
Once more, FLY! Reaching far into the sky with a pounding heart.
奇想天外に彩ったんだ Dream☆Story
A wildly colored Dream☆Story!
やっぱ1秒たりとも目を離して欲しいな
I want you to keep your eyes on me every single second.
瞬きもしてらんない
You won't even have time to blink!
あぁほらね 最高でしょ？ イエーイ！
Ah, see? Isn't it amazing? Yeah!
おー！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
懐かしいですね〜
So nostalgic~
ね！なんだかんだ
Right! Somehow or another...
今回はですね、宝石をイメージしてステージを作ってもらいました！
This time, we had a stage created with the image of gemstones!
すごい！だってもほろらいぶの初のライブなので！
Amazing! Because it's Hololive's first live, after all!
気合入れてもらっちゃったよね〜！
We really got fired up for it~!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
そして、先ほど歌ったのがドリームストーリーだったんですけど、後ろに映像が流れてましたよね？
And the song we just sang was Dream Story, but footage was playing in the background, right?
えっ、流れてた？私見てたぞ、これ
Eh, was it playing? I was watching this.
あちらですね、ファーストフェスの時の映像だったということで、なんと4年半前でございます！
That, as it turns out, was footage from the 1st Fest, which was 4 and a half years ago!
すごーい！歴史を感じるね、やっぱ見ただけでもわかるしね、なんかね
Amazing! You can feel the history, you can tell just by looking at it, right?
なんか私たちもさ、見た目めっちゃ変わってない？
Also, don't our appearances look like they've changed a lot?
そうだよね、成長したんだよ、成長したんだよ
That's right, we grew up, we grew up.
みんなダンスも成長したよね、あんな時ね、この、この踊りも
Everyone's dancing has also grown, back then, this dance too...
なんか、はずかし、はずかしすぎたな、ね、えもいな
Somehow, it's so embarrassing, so embarrassing, right, how emotional.
そんなね、私たち、今日はね、お互いのいろんな曲を歌っていくので、どんな曲を歌うか楽しみにしていてください！
So, we are going to sing various songs of each other today, so please look forward to what songs we'll sing!
はーい！
Yay!
では、早速ですが、次の曲に行きますよ！
Well then, without further ado, we're going to the next song!
はーい！
Yay!
準備していきまーす！
Let's get ready!
飛んでいけな めちゃ進む 年頃の少女遊びたいよ
Fly away, charging ahead, girls of this age want to play!
ハジメノイッポ 作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
[Title: Hajime no Ippo / Lyrics & Music: Nayutan Seijin]
前人未踏のときめき知りたい人
Anyone wanting to know unprecedented excitement?
一回と言いづらい？今だっていいじゃない？
Hard to say just once? Isn't now fine too?
キューボ音通り遊びたい人
Anyone wanting to play along to the cue beat?
それって君じゃない？今日は一体いいじゃない？
Isn't that you? Isn't today just fine?
育ったまんまのマネ けじめつけそう 人生の醍醐味です
Imitating how we grew up, looking like we're setting things straight is the spice of life!
一歩引いてダッシュ そんでハートダッシュ この作戦 もう怪しい角はない
Step back and dash, then heart dash! There's nothing suspicious about this strategy anymore!
動かなかった足を 今は踏み出したいと燃える 一人ではできなかったこと
Feet that wouldn't move, now burning with the desire to step forward. Things I couldn't do alone...
やっちゃおうよ！行っちゃおうよ！
Let's do it! Let's go!
一歩一歩進んでいくぞ 群青の空調子切るわ まだまだ
Step by step, we'll forge ahead! We'll set the tone in the ultramarine sky, still not enough!
でも一歩一歩って進んでいくぞ 声がわれらの第一歩 近くで見といてくだサイな
But step by step, we keep going! Our voices are our very first step, watch us closely from nearby!
転んだり迷ったり浮き足立って もうちょっと付き合ってくだサイませ 余裕せったときは逃げ足なんて起こしません
Falling, getting lost, getting restless, please bear with us a little longer! When we get flustered, we won't run away!
飛んでいけな めちゃ進む 年頃の少女遊びたいよ
Fly away, charging ahead, girls of this age want to play!
一歩一歩進んでいくぞ 群青の空調子切るわ まだまだ
Step by step, we'll forge ahead! We'll set the tone in the ultramarine sky, still not enough!
もしかして今とてもいい感じ？
Maybe right now is a really good vibe?
もっとギア上げちゃっていい感じ？
Is it okay to crank up the gear even more?
今日という日は？
What day is today?
だからめいっぱい声を出してみよう Let's go!
So let's raise our voices to the max, Let's go!
世界中大きく！さあもっともう一回！宇宙イチ楽しく！
Make the whole world big! Come on, once more! Make it the most fun in the universe!
うん、めっちゃ最高！
Yep, absolutely the best!
少しもやっていた未来に今は期待とかしちゃってみる 君がいたから見れた景色
In a future that was a bit hazy, now I'm starting to have expectations. The scenery I could see because you were here!
やっちゃおうよ！行っちゃおうよ！
Let's do it! Let's go!
一歩一歩って突っ込んだものの どんどん待ってるでかい世界にクラクラ
Rushing in step by step, but getting dizzy at the huge world waiting for us!
でも一歩一歩って大事にするぞ それがわれらの第一歩
But we'll cherish every single step, that is our very first step!
一歩一歩って進んでいくぞ 群青の空調子切るわ もうすぐ
Step by step, we'll forge ahead! We'll set the tone in the ultramarine sky very soon!
この一歩一歩を楽しんでいくぞ それじゃみんなで第一歩
We'll enjoy every single step, and now everyone takes the first step!
近くで見といてくだサイな 転んだり迷ったり浮き足立って もうちょっと付き合ってくだサイませ 余裕せったときは逃げ足なんて起こしません
Watch us closely, falling, getting lost, getting restless, please bear with us a little longer! When we get flustered, we won't run away!
ずっと見ていてくだサイな 揃ってる外してる 未来鳴らせ 両手棒をご覧くだサイませ
Please keep watching us, aligned or out of sync, making our future ring, please behold with both hands!
こんなときのこころ退屈なんて感じません
In times like this, we never feel bored!
飛んでいけな めちゃ進む 年頃の少女遊びたいよ
Fly away, charging ahead, girls of this age want to play!
ダメダメ ダメダメ やっぱっぱっぱ パーリナイしたい
No way, no way, no way, no way, we totally wanna party!
シュガーラッシュ 作詞・作曲：DECO*27 編曲：TAKINOUE
[Title: Sugar Rush / Lyrics & Music: DECO*27 / Arrangement: TAKU INOUE]
空っぽっぽい表情で また◯ or ✕ ？ オーライがってん
With a hollow-looking expression, once again circle or cross? Alright, got it!
Lovely? Cutie? Sexy? Pretty? Cool? or Chic?
今日はどのアタシで攻めてみましょうか
Which approach should I charge in with today?
絶対領域コントラスト 思考錯誤して
View in full contrast, any falter could make the break.
キミの視線独占間違いなしでしょ
I'll make sure your gaze is mine to keep soon enough.
望んで 願って もっともっと求めて
I want it, I need it, come on now, give it up already.
なんでもなれるのキミの思い通り
Whatever you want, whoever you want, I aim to please.
着せ替えて 変身させて
Put on a dress, change my face,
もうどうにでもして ついでに抱きしめて!
whatever you need, all I need is your loving embrace!
Baby Maniacs! 溺れちゃうの
Baby Maniacs! Drown me in your love,
はやくあたしを連れ出して
hurry up and carry me away.
ねえ夢中なんだ この瞳にうつるのはひとりだけ
Hey, I may be crazy, but I'll make sure that you only ever look my way.
ふらふらしてて掴まれない 気分屋でマイペース
It's just out of reach now, can't get a grip on my pace,
必殺らぶら光線届きません
those beams are beyond my perception.
そんで視線交差しません なんで?わかりません
You've yet to look, why wait? I don't understand.
キミ成分が足りません!
Don't you know I'm the one you want?
望んで 願って もっともっと求めて
I want it, I need it, come on now, give it up already.
なんでもなれるのキミの思い通り
Whatever you want, whoever you want, I aim to please.
叶えさせて 変わらせて
So just make a wish, and then I'll grant it,
絶対ハート射止めにしてやるから覚悟して!
your heart will be shot down soon, don't forget!
Baby boy! 中毒とまんない
Baby boy! Just wanna take a bite,
はやくあたしを奪って
hurry up and take me far away.
ねえ眼中ないの? その瞳には誰が映っているの?
Hey, are you blind, who's the one on your radar this time around?
キミを振り向かせる為なら どんな手でも使うわ
If I could only just get you to catch my gaze, I'll use any means necessary.
超絶俺様主義のキミに合うのはあたしだけ
I'm the only one who's good enough for you in the end.
ねえあたしの中キミだけなんだ
Yeah, you're the only one I need, open your eyes to the truth.
知らないフリはやめてよ
Please stop this ache in my heart,
この胸の痛みを止めてよ
pull the trigger and take me down!
Baby Maniacs! 溺れちゃうの
Baby Maniacs! Drown me in your love,
はやくあたしを連れ出して
hurry up and carry me away.
ねえ夢中なんだ この瞳にうつるのはひとりだけ
Hey, I may be crazy, but I'll make sure that you only ever look my way.
なんで多幸なんなの? なにな不満なんなの?
Why are you so scared? What drives you freakin' mad?
なんて理不尽に叫んでみたり
Why not choose insanity? Oh come, don't make me scream.
I love you! I need you! あたしはキミにあうために生まれてきたの!
I love you! I need you! I was born to meet you and give you all of my love!
Baby Maniacs! 溺れちゃうの はやくあたしを連れ出して
Baby Maniacs! Drown me in your love, hurry up and carry me away.
ねえ夢中なんだ この瞳にうつるのはひとりだけ
Hey, I may be crazy, but I'll make sure that you only ever look my way.
ふらふらしてて掴まれない 気分屋でマイペース
It's just out of reach now, can't get a grip on my pace,
必殺らぶら光線届きません
those beams are beyond my perception.
そんで視線交差しません なんで?わかりません
You've yet to look, why wait? I don't understand.
キミ成分が足りません!
Don't you know I'm the one you want?
望んで 願って もっともっと求めて
I want it, I need it, come on now, give it up already.
なんでもなれるのキミの思い通り
Whatever you want, whoever you want, I aim to please.
叶えさせて 変わらせて
So just make a wish, and then I'll grant it,
絶対ハート射止めにしてやるから覚悟して!
your heart will be shot down soon, don't forget!
推し変なんて許さないんだから馬鹿にしてんじゃいの?
You can't just move on to someone else, are you making a fool of me?
Baby Maniacs! 溺れちゃうの はやくあたしを連れ出して
Baby Maniacs! Drown me in your love, hurry up and carry me away.
だめだめだめだめ おーいぇい!
No, no, no, no, oh yeah!
箱にあたる陽を横目で眺めて
Glancing sideways at the sunlight hitting the box,
そっと陰る木の根に一人で比べていた
I compared myself alone at the roots of the quietly shading tree.
積もる溜息を吹き払うように
As if blowing away the piling sighs,
そんな私を見つけてくれたんだ
you were the one who found me like that.
そう それは恋のようなぬくもりを
Yes, wrapping all that warmth like love
君に笑顔咲かせたら
and making a smile bloom on your face,
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
in the sky dancing with the cherry blossom breeze, at the place where I met you,
どれくらいの思い出ぎゅっと溢れそうになるかな
I wonder how many memories are about to overflow.
君と流した涙は 明日の笑顔の糧にしよう
The tears we shed together will become nourishment for tomorrow's smiles.
膝をついていたってほら 何度だっていいよ
Even if we fell to our knees, see, any number of times is fine.
意地を張って 恥をかいて
Putting up pride, feeling embarrassed,
君が傍で見守ってくれたから
knowing that you watched over me by my side,
追い風を受けてとまらない日々も
even days when we couldn't stop under a tailwind,
そっと挫けそうになって心が疼いた
softly felt like giving up and my heart ached.
積もる溜息でまた泣きかけても
Even if I almost cried again with piling sighs,
あたたかな手でずっと支えてくれたんだ
you always supported me with your warm hands.
追い風を受けてとまらない日々も
Even days when we couldn't stop under a tailwind,
そっと挫けそうになって心が疼いた
softly felt like giving up and my heart ached.
積もる溜息でまた泣きかけても
Even if I almost cried again with piling sighs,
あたたかな手でずっと支えてくれた
you always supported me with your warm hands.
箱にあたる陽を横目で眺めて
Looking sideways at the sunlight hitting the box,
そっと陰る木に一人で比べてた
I compared myself alone to the quietly darkening tree.
積もる溜息を吹き払うように
As if to blow away the piling sighs,
そんな私が見つけてくれたんだ
You were the one who found me like that.
そう それは恋のような ぬくもりを全部
Yes, it's like love, all that warmth,
君に笑顔咲かせるなら
If it makes a smile bloom on your face.
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
In this place where I met you, dancing in the cherry blossom breeze,
どれくらいの思い出ぎゅっと 溢れそうになるかな
I wonder how many memories are about to overflow.
君と流した涙は 明日の笑顔の糧にしよう
Let's turn the tears we shed together into nourishment for tomorrow's smiles.
膝をついてたってほら 何度だっていいよ
Even if we dropped to our knees, hey, any number of times is fine.
意地を張って 恥をかいて
Putting on airs, making a fool of myself,
君が傍で見守ってくれたから わかっているから
You watched over me by my side, and I know that.
追い風を受けてとまれない日々も
Even on days when I can't stop with a tailwind,
そっと挫けそうになって心が疼いた
My heart ached as I felt like giving up quietly.
積もる溜息でまた泣きかけても
Even if I start crying again from piling sighs,
あたたかな手でずっと支えてくれたんだ
You always supported me with your warm hands.
ほら 耳を澄ませば 一人じゃないから
Hey, if you listen closely, you're not alone.
諦めかけて心が閉じてても
Even when I gave up and my heart closed,
君が背中を押してくれたよね
You pushed me on the back, didn't you?
春の蕾が花開く頃は 隣で笑い合おうね
When spring buds bloom into flowers, let's laugh together side by side.
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
In this place where I met you, dancing in the cherry blossom breeze,
どれくらいの思い出ぎゅっと 溢れそうになるかな
I wonder how many memories are about to overflow.
君と描くこの花は 未来もきっと残るから
The flower we draw together will surely remain in the future too.
汗をかいた分はそうさ 強くなれるんだ
The sweat we shed—that's right, it makes us stronger.
意地を張って 恥をかいて
Putting on airs, making a fool of myself,
君が傍で見守ってくれたから ありがとうだよ
Thank you for watching over me by my side.
君と出逢えたこの空 これからももっと咲かせ続けるよ
In this sky where I met you, I'll keep making it bloom even more from now on.
いつか描いた文字の中
Inside the words I drew someday,
目を閉じた先に 色づく景色が揺れた
Beyond closed eyes, a colorful scenery swayed.
少し戸惑う風の中
Inside a slightly bewildering wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping petals, our voices.
一瞬 一瞬 捕らえるみたいに
Like capturing every single moment,
もっと もっと 踏み出せたら
If we could step forward more and more,
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect the "us" of right now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because a piece of you is in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
Even if we aren't strong, let's release today's light
僕と君と初め 空に放つ
into the sky together with you.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
Because we'll make this miracle shine gently together,
力が湧くから
strength wells up from within.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clenching a new seed in hand,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め蒔いた
I sowed it with a strong wish toward the distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow,
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
Petals of ideals, praying in tomorrow's sky.
何百 億も光る星みたいに
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars,
ずっと ずっと 終わらないから
It will never, ever end,
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile strongly embraces the past,
今 未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
Extending this hand to the future right now.
時に転んでも 空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes, let's look up at the sky.
笑い 日々を刻んでゆく
Laughing, we carve out our days,
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから
Promising to seize our next dream.
踏み出そうここから
Let's step forward from right here.
(We are with you We are with you)
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future.
あの夢手に入れたい
I want to make that dream mine.
(We are with you Capture The Moment)
触れた奇跡の中で
Inside the miracle we touched,
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
If we blend into the sky stretching beyond,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
I want to connect your place with the present.
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now...
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because a piece of you is in this heart,
強くなくてもいい
we don't have to be strong.
今の光を
Gathering today's light,
僕と君と集め 空に放つ
with you and me, released into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
We'll gently make this miracle shine together,
咲かせようここから
let's make it bloom from here.
一人じゃないから
'Cause we're not alone,
[we are one]
褪せたハナミドリ
[Title: Faded Hanamidori]
恋人に恋い焦がれるのか 気づかなかったハヤリの唄
Am I yearning for a lover? I missed that popular song.
喉が出たくらい甘い甘いごとで 包まれた君 軽いのか寂しいみたい
Wrapped in things so sweet it makes your throat ache, you seem fickle, or rather, lonely.
まいいよ 輪郭なセリフで飾って 好きよわめきを途切れずそそって
It's fine, decorate with outlined lines, pour your affection without a break.
愛嬌ごとでやってさして 人も憐れなケモノを急いで
Acting cute and letting them do it, hurrying poor beasts too.
永遠の愛なんて 建て前どこにもありゃしない 信じたいけど
There's no such thing as eternal love anywhere, though I want to believe it.
どうせ枯れゆく俗らそら世界で愛が
Anyway, in this worldly sky where things wither away, love is...
ただ綺麗な言葉はいらない
Just beautiful words aren't needed.
未来へこうとずれない世界なら 揃えていそとめて
If it's a world that doesn't slip toward the future, line them up and stop them.
枯れた思い出に浮くハナミドリ 二人肩並べ歩いたメグロ通りの桜
A dogwood floating on withered memories, cherry blossoms on Meguro Street where we walked side by side.
いつまでもずっとこのままでいようね ささやいた声のまやかし
'Let's stay like this forever,' whispered voices, mere illusions.
燃えそフラズナ街をさまよって 疲れないや続けるよって
Wandering through the burning yet purposeless town, 'I won't get tired, I'll keep going,' you said.
身を委ねちゃおうか 私だって寂しかったもの
Shall I surrender myself? After all, I was lonely too.
素敵な罪を重ねても あなたは振り返りはしない 分かってるけど
Even if we pile up wonderful sins, you won't look back—even though I know that.
どうせ果てせる結実俗らそら世界で愛が
Anyway, in this worldly sky where results bear fruit, love is...
あんなに好きを重ねていたって
Even though we piled up so much love,
今じゃもう何事もなかったかのように 外れてしまうなんて
now it feels as though nothing ever happened, slipping away like that.
さよなら 感情もう戻れないや そんだけ大きな恋をしたんだ
Goodbye, my feelings can't go back anymore. That's how big of a love I fell into.
全て空からの嘘に見えても 愛を探していく
Even if everything looks like a lie from the sky, I'll keep searching for love.
叶わない俗らそら世界で愛が
In this unfulfillable, worldly sky, love is...
ただ綺麗な言葉はいらない
Just beautiful words aren't needed.
未来へこうとずれない世界なら 揃えていそとめて
If it's a world that doesn't slip toward the future, line them up and stop them.
ひらり ふらり さまよっていく
Fluttering, wandering away,
白い夢はもうやめた
I've already quit white dreams.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I'd known all along, lured by the scent as I fall down.
与えられた役割を尋ねることが怖くて
Terrified to ask what role was given to me,
流れる日々の答えに濁したのは心だけ
only my heart clouded over the answers of flowing days.
さだめられた箱の中 味気ない現実(ナイトメア)に
Inside the prescribed box, into a bland nightmare,
少し青信じてたんだ 迷い込みもしないまま
I believed in pale blue slightly, without even straying.
しまい隠したはずだった 暖かな体温(ぬくもり)をと分かっている
I should've hidden away the warm comfort, knowing full well—
奥に歪むその目で 見た紛れもない衝動を
with eyes warped deep inside, the undeniable impulse I saw—
ひらり ふらり 飛んでゆける 迷い窓口閉じ込めた
Fluttering and flying away, locking up the stray window—
あなたはもう話さないで やがて嘘と知っても
You won't let go anymore, even knowing it's a lie eventually.
ひらり ふらり さまよっていく
Fluttering, wandering away,
白い夢はもうやめた
I've already quit white dreams.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I'd known all along, lured by the scent as I fall down.
まとわり付く言葉だけ 何の意味もないくせに
Clinging words carry no meaning whatsoever,
背を濡らしてる重さに 潰れそうでもがいていた
struggling as if crushed by the weight wetting my back.
気づかないふりをしていたの かわすすべては囁いた
I was pretending not to notice; everything exchanged whispered—
罠に染まる覚悟のこと 確かめるのはそれだけ
the resolve to be dyed in the trap is all to confirm.
ひらり ふらり 迷い降りてく 迷い窓口脱ぎ捨てて
Fluttering and wandering down, casting off the stray window—
あなたはもう話さないで やがて嘘と知っても
You won't let go anymore, even knowing it's a lie eventually.
ひらり ふらり 落とされてゆく 白い夢はもうやめた
Fluttering, being dropped away, I've quit white dreams.
私きっと戻れない 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I surely can't go back, lured by the scent as I fall down.
ひらり ふらり 飛んでゆける 迷い窓口閉じ込めた
Fluttering and flying away, locking up the stray window—
あなたはもう話さないで やがて嘘と知っても
You won't let go anymore, even knowing it's a lie eventually.
ひらり ふらり さまよっていく 白い夢はもうやめた
Fluttering, wandering away, I've quit white dreams.
私ずっと知ってたの 匂いに誘われて落ちてく
I'd known all along, lured by the scent as I fall down.
息をしている だから生きている
I am breathing, therefore I am alive.
何度もずっと言葉をお化粧してきたんだ
Countless times, I've always dressed up my words.
息をしている ように見えている
I seem to be breathing, or so it looks.
青が染み出す 私にとっての何か
Blue oozes out—something precious to me...
孤独がとくとくしている
Loneliness throbs steadily,
ここはいつも変わらずに
and this place remains unchanged always,
塞ぎ続ける ことひとつの
just one thing continuing to seal...
最後まで私のこと覚えててくれるの
Will you remember me until the very end?
消えてしまいそうなの わかってよ わかってよね
Knowing I might just fade away,
please understand... please understand me.
本音も建前も いつかは卒業するんでしょ
True feelings and facades... we'll graduate from them someday, right?
日常に戻ったら 私はいなくなるの
Once we return to everyday life,
I will disappear.
命のような夢を見てるよ またね バイバイ
I'm dreaming a dream like life itself...
See you later, bye-bye.
息をしている だから生きている
I'm breathing, therefore I'm alive.
見た目と中身の 境界線をまたいでも戻って 音が止まって
Even if I cross the boundary of appearance and reality and return,
the sound stops,
動かなくなって そんな私を君は笑ってくれるかな
and I stop moving.
Can you smile at a me like that?
孤独が特効薬している
Loneliness is serving as a special remedy,
ここはいつも変わらずに
and this place remains unchanged as always,
巡り続ける 希望にしたいの 命
wanting to turn it into hope that keeps spinning round and round: life.
最後まで私のこと 見届けてくれるの
Will you watch over me until the very end?
縋ってしまいそうなの わかってよ わかってよね
Clinging to you like this,
please understand... please understand me.
真実をつないだら もう二度と戻せないのに
Once we string truths together,
we can never go back again,
君が忘れちゃったら 私はいなくなるの
yet if you forget, I will disappear.
命のような夢を見てるよ またね バイバイ
I'm dreaming a dream like life itself...
See you later, bye-bye.
行き急いだあの日の傷を 軽くいじらないで はがして
Don't lightly fiddle with the scars
of that hurried day—peel them off instead.
それが生き抜く糧になるから
Because that will become
the nourishment to survive.
大丈夫 ずっと私は 歌い続けるから
It's alright, I will keep on singing forever.
最後まで私もう生きているか分からないけど 君がくれた言葉は確実に残ってる
I don't know if I'll be alive until the very end,
but the words you gave me definitely remain.
最後まで私を覚えていなくてもいいから 死んでしまうんだろう わかんない わかんないよ
Even if you don't remember me until the end, that's fine...
I might die, I don't know, I really don't know.
でも 今君が笑ったこと それだけで意味があること
But right now, just the fact that you smiled—
that alone gives it meaning.
君が忘れちゃっても 私は死なないから
Even if you forget, I won't die, so
命のような夢を見てるよ またね バイバイ
I'm dreaming a dream like life itself...
See you later, bye-bye.
ここに宣言します！ セブンスホイッスル
I hereby declare! The 7th Whistle!
ラッキーセブンスホイッスル 作詩:まつもとみなか 作曲・編曲:藤原彩蝶
[Song: Lucky 7th Whistle / Lyrics: Minaka Matsumoto / Music: Ayacho Fujiwara]
1つ病める時も 健やかなる時も ずっと
1: Whether in sickness or in health, forever
愛を歌い続けることを 堂々と誓います
I proudly vow to keep on singing of love.
2つ トークとかダンスももっと追求します
2: I will pursue my talk and dance even further!
3つ ずっと推してもらえる アイドルになってみせます
3: I'll prove to be an idol
you can always support!
アイドルになって魅せます
I'll make you an idol!
4つめ 不安な未来も
4th, a future of anxiety too,
私が照らすんだ
I'm going to shine a light on it.
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days when I feel down,
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔 その声
I remember everyone's smiles and voices.
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution,
サンデーマンデーこの先ずっと
Sunday, Monday, from here on out,
一緒だよね 約束 ほらね 笑う門にはソラ来たる
It's always going to be together, right? It's a promise!
ハッピーバースデイ 毎日が ほら
Happy Birthday every single day,
チューズデイ ウェンズデイ ラッキーデイ
Tuesday, Wednesday, Lucky Day.
生まれ変わっても 迷わずに
No matter how I'm reborn, without getting lost,
君だけのアイドルになるよ
I'll become your one and only idol!
何度も見つけてね セブンスホイッスル
Find me over and over again, Seven's Whistle.
5つめ アイドルとは時にあざとくがお決まりと
5th, "Idols can be quite clumsy sometimes,"
誰かが言ってたけど上手ができないのです
someone once said, but I'm not very good at it.
ねえ 6つめ 私からお願い聞いて
Hey, 6th, listen to my request:
相思相愛 推し変なんてしないでよね
Mutually loving, don't ever change your oshi, okay?
私を見て！！
Look at me!!
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution,
サンデーマンデーこの先ずっと
Sunday, Monday, from here on out,
一緒だよね 約束
It's always going to be together, right? It's a promise!
みんな 笑う門にはソラ来たる
Everyone, smiles bring Sora to you!
ハッピーバースデイ 毎日が ほら
Happy Birthday every single day,
チューズデイ ウェンズデイ エブリデイ
Tuesday, Wednesday, Everyday,
7つめ 全身全霊かけて
7th, putting body and soul into it,
ここにいるみんなのことを 永遠に愛します
I will love everyone here forever.
セブンスホイッスル
Seven's Whistle!
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution,
サンデーマンデーこの先ずっと
Sunday, Monday, from here on out,
一緒だよね 約束 ほらね 笑う門にはソラ来たる
It's always going to be together, right? It's a promise!
ハッピーバースデイ 毎日が ほら
Happy Birthday every single day,
チューズデイ ウェンズデイ ラッキーデイ
Tuesday, Wednesday, Lucky Day.
生まれ変わっても 迷わずに
No matter how I'm reborn, without getting lost,
君だけのアイドルになるよ
I'll become your one and only idol!
何度も見つけてね セブンスホイッスル
Find me over and over again, Seven's Whistle.
永遠に愛します セブンスホイッスル
I will love you forever, Seven's Whistle!
ハッピーラッキーセブン革命
Happy Lucky Seven Revolution!
何のポーズ？
What pose is this?
え、わかんない、え、何？
Eh, I don't know, eh, what?
私、どうしよう、こ、こ...
What should I do, like...
あ、いいじゃなーい！
Ah, that's nice!
いいじゃなーい！いいじゃなーい！
That's nice! That's nice!
パシャパシャパシャパシャ...
Snap, snap, snap, snap...
い、1度プリンセスみたいに...
Princess style...
え？プリンセス、ほかには？
Eh? Princess? What else?
なんか、客席側お...
Like, facing the audience...
あ、たしかに！客席さーん！客席さーん！
Ah, true! Audience-san! Audience-san!
こっちでーす！
Over here!
え？待って、客席、そ、そ...
Eh? Wait, audience, s-, s-...
そ、そう！そ、そ...
Y-, yes! S-, s-...
待ってこれさ、この流れ知ってる？
Wait, do you know this routine?
そらちゃんの、ゼロキサの時も毎回...
Sora-chan's and Zerokisa's, every time...
ねぇドクター ねぇドクター
Hey doctor, hey doctor,
免許捨ててよ特段 まだいつものレイのバッグ
throw away your license, especially that usual bag.
ハッピー アンラッキー 行き来するモード
Happy, unlucky, switching modes,
組み立てて 全脳意識のまごころ
assembling the sincerity of whole-brain consciousness.
ちっちっちっちっちっちっとっと ねじまいって
Tick-tock tick-tock, wind it up,
おかしいね おかしいね くだらないね やいやい
isn't it strange? It's silly, yay yay.
訳ないね 訳ないね ハイスペックなんだぜ
It's no problem at all, it's high-spec.
最先端のフォーム やらなきゃそう 時々が止まりそう
State-of-the-art form, if I don't do it, time seems to stop,
ねじまいて リルビなってよ 顔をそむけて
wind it up, turn into Rirubi, look away,
ねじまいてねじまいてよ
wind it up, wind it up.
ちょっとだけね ピッポパッポ鳴らして 夢をつくる
Just a little, ringing pippo-pappo, making dreams.
ちょっとだけね でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち となくなっちゃうかも
Just a little, but if it's just a little, it might disappear soon.
リルビリルビリルビリルビ リルビリルビリルビもっと
Rirubi rirubi rirubi rirubi, more rirubi!
ちっちっちっちっちっちっとっと ねじまいって ときめいてよ
Tick-tock tick-tock, wind it up, make it flutter with excitement.
ついに来たよ お待たせ 街にまた...
Finally it's here, making you wait, meeting in town...
2次元の世界からやってきた
Coming from a 2D world,
ふざけわけば チャームにご愛嬌で
playfully with charm and cuteness,
私はそう エリート なんていったって エリート
I am elite, no matter what, elite.
そんな予定表に決まってるじゃん いじわるも なき虫も
It's bound to be on schedule, teasing and crybabies too,
神対応も かき集めたら みこパワーで 幸せわけわけして
gathering great service, sharing happiness with Miko power.
ロボ子は エリートで！
Roboco is elite!
みみみみみこみこみこで ほりほりうんちゃらかんちゃら
Miko miko miko, digging and yada yada,
みみみみみこみこみこで きゅんときはほりゃにゃにゃにゃ
Miko miko miko, when making a heart, nya nya nya.
幸せのペコ ポンぷにみみ みんな笑顔あれ
Happy peko pon, soft ears, everyone smile.
画面の中の君が初めて 手につけた時
When I first got my hands on you inside the screen,
なぜかここから 揺さぶられたんだ
for some reason, I was shaken right from here.
つくり まといに 命を宿す 君の...
Breathing life into the creation you wear...
言いかけた言葉を飲み込んで
Swallowing the words I started to say,
あれっ 不具合かな
Huh, is this a bug?
楽しそうな君は素敵だった
You looked so happy, you were wonderful.
画面の中の君が好き
I love you inside the screen,
その化粧をした君の顔が…
That makeup-wearing face of yours...
ただ君が笑えたならいい
As long as you could smile,
本当の君と
Even if the real you
実は違うとしても 新しい扉を開けて
Is actually different, open a new door.
息をしようよ 嘘の本当の関係ないから
Let's breathe, because fake or real doesn't matter.
息をしてる瞬間を僕らに届けたいんだ
I want to deliver the moment we're breathing to you
君が好きだから
Because I love you.
見送るソワレ 僕ら目撃者だ
Seeing off the soiree, we are witnesses,
急に手を伸ばした
I suddenly reached out my hand.
水平線がただねじだって
Even if the horizon is just twisted,
止めどなく日々をつなぐ架け橋わたったら
Once we cross the bridge connecting our ceaseless days,
いつの聞いたソワレ 君に届くまでさ
Soiree, whenever I heard it, until it reaches you,
何度でも 呼び声を…
No matter how many times, I'll call out...
清らかな奇跡届いて
May a pure miracle reach you,
行くせいその果て どこまでも
To the ends of our journey, no matter where.
また叩いたソワレ 未だネイキッド
Beating again, soiree, still naked,
太陽の目を結んで ダイダロスさ
Tying the sun's eyes, like Daedalus,
逃げ出したソゼ 明日まだ明き空を
Escaping sose, tomorrow's still open sky
またぐしおりを挟んだら
If I tuck in a bookmark stepping across,
約束のソワレ 僕が眠るまでは
Promised soiree, until I fall asleep,
何度でも また明日
No matter how many times, see you tomorrow.
背景ソワレ 君へ呼び継がれる僕たちの物語
Background soiree, our story passed down to you.
昨日から止まったような
A clock that seemed to have stopped since yesterday,
時計 幼い幼い
Childhood, so young...
この胸ふと 思い出したんだ
I suddenly remembered in my heart.
もう心配しなくてもいいよ
"You don't have to worry anymore."
あの優しい声がそばにあったから
Because that gentle voice was always by my side.
恋に傷ついて 道に迷った日もあったけれど
There were days when I was hurt by love and lost my way,
いつだって探してたのは輝くはずのベラデイエブリデイ
I was always looking for a better day that should shine, everyday.
解き放てなその感情 時代の背にしたってつまらないよ
Unleash that emotion; it's boring to blame the times.
everyday 君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Everyday, even if you are, there are days when you stop,
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Step and Go!! Everyday
君であれ 立ち止まる日もあるけれど
Even if you stop sometimes,
ねえきっと君は大丈夫
Hey, I'm sure you'll be fine.
Step and Go!! Step and Go!!
お別れしたのは もっと 前のことだったような
It seems like it was a long time ago that we said goodbye...
悲しい光は封じ込めて かかとをすり減らしたんだ
Keeping the sad light inside, wearing down my heels.
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
When I was with you I could see it, now I can't anymore.
透明な彗星をぼんやりと でもそれだけ探している
Looking dimly for a transparent comet, but that's all I'm looking for.
しょっちゅう歌を歌ったよ その時だけのメロディーを
I often sang songs, melodies just for those moments.
寂しくなんかなかったよ ちゃんと寂しくなれたから
I wasn't lonely, because I was able to feel truly lonely.
いつまでどこまでなんて 正常か異常かなんて
Wondering how far or until when, what's normal or abnormal,
考える暇も無い程 歩くのは大変だ
There's not even time to think, walking is so hard.
楽しい方がずっといいよ ごまかして笑っていくよ
It's much better to have fun, I'll just fake it and smile.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消やしない
Don't worry, that pain won't go away even if you forget.
理想で作った道を 現実が塗り替えていくよ
Reality rewrites the road we made with our ideals.
思い出はその軌道の上で 輝きになって残っている
Memories remain, shining brightly on that path.
お別れしたのは何で 何のためだったんだろうな
I wonder why and for what we said goodbye.
悲しい光が僕の影を 前に長く伸ばしている
The sad light stretches my shadow long before me.
時々熱が出るよ 時間がある時眠るよ
Sometimes I get a fever, and sleep when I have time.
夢だと解るその中で 君と会ってからまた行こう
Knowing it's a dream, I'll see you there and then go again.
晴天とはほど遠い 終わらない暗闇にも
Far from clear skies, even in the never-ending darkness,
星を思い浮かべたら すぐ銀河の中だ
If I imagine the stars, I'm right inside the galaxy.
あまり泣かなくなっても 靴を新しくしても
Even if I don't cry as much, even with new shoes,
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消やしない
Don't worry, that pain won't go away even if you forget.
伝えたかった事が きっとあったんだろうな
There must have been something I wanted to tell you.
恐らくありきたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
It's probably a cliché, but even so...
お別れした事は 出会った事と繋がっている
What we said goodbye to is connected to what we met.
あの透明な彗星は 透明だから無くならない
That transparent comet will never disappear because it's transparent.
〇×どれかなんて 皆と比べてどうかなんて
Wondering if it's right or wrong, how I compare to everyone,
確かめる間も無い程 生きるのは最高だ
There's no time to check, living life is simply wonderful.
あまり泣かなくなっても ごまかして笑っていくよ
Even if I don't cry as much, I'll just fake it and smile.
大丈夫だ あの痛みは 忘れたって消やしない
Don't worry, that pain won't go away even if you forget.
大丈夫だ この光の 始まりには 君がいる
Don't worry, you are at the beginning of this light.
みんな、0期生ライブを見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for watching the 0th Generation live!
早速ですが、告知の時間です！
Without further ado, it's time for some announcements!
まずは、こちら！
First up is this!
0期生ライブ記念グッズが出ます！イエーイ！
The 0th Gen Live commemorative merchandise is out! Yay!
それでは順番に紹介していくね。一つ目は、こちら！
Now I'll introduce them in order. First one is this!
アクリルスタンド！トビ先生が書いてくれました！
Acrylic stands! Drawn by Tobi-sensei!
みんなの分があるのでぜひ全員分集めてください！
There's one for everyone, so please collect them all!
次は、こちら！ロボ子紹介お願い！
Next is this! Roboco-san, please introduce it!
はーい！こちらはガーランド風キーホルダー！
Coming right up! This is a garland-style keychain!
ガーランドをイメージしたアクリルチャームです！
It's an acrylic charm inspired by a garland!
それぞれをお繋ぎして飾ることができるので、0期生みんな繋げてってね！
You can connect and display them together, so make sure to connect all of 0th Gen!
次はみこち！
Next is Mikochi!
はーい！次はネックストラップ付きチケットケースです！
Coming right up! Next is the ticket case with neck strap!
イベントのチケットなど入れられるネックストラップ付きのチケットケースです！
It's a ticket case with a neck strap that can hold event tickets and more!
背景台紙付きで、ケースの中にアクリルスタンドを入れて持ち運んでね！
It comes with a background mount, and you can put the acrylic stand inside!
はい、次はランダム缶バッジ！
Yes, next is the random button badge!
華やかなデザインの缶バッジになっております！
These are button badges with a gorgeous design!
全10種のランダム仕様になっているので、ぜひたくさん集めてください！
There are 10 random types in total, so please collect lots of them!
次はAZKiちゃん！
Next is AZKi-chan!
はい、次はブランケット！
Yes, next is the blanket!
今回の記念キービジュアルを大きく使用したブランケットになっております！
This blanket prominently features the main commemorative key visual!
冬のお供にいかがでしょうか？というわけで、そらちゃんにお戻しします！
How about it as a winter companion? With that, I'll pass it back to Sora-chan!
はい！みんなありがとう！
Yes! Thank you everyone!
まだありますよ！
There's still more!
ブロマイドケース！
Bromide case!
0期生を応援してくれてるファンのみんなへ、
For all the fans supporting 0th Gen,
0期生全員からのメッセージ入りのブロマイドケースだよ！
it's a bromide case with messages from all 0th Gen members!
メッセージは届いてからのお楽しみ！
The messages are a surprise until they arrive!
内容は複製になるのでお気を付けください！
Please note that the contents are replicas!
はいというわけでグッズは以上になります！
Yes, so that's all for the goods!
もりだくさんだったね！
There were a lot, weren't there?
今回は数量限定やセット販売はないので好きなものを単品でたくさんお買い求めください！
This time there are no made-to-order limits or set sales, so please buy plenty individually!
まずは私、ときのそらから！
First is me, Tokino Sora!
先ほどの私の7周年記念配信でも言いましたが、ときのそら7周年記念グッズもありますのでよろしくお願いします！
As I mentioned in my 7th anniversary stream earlier, there are also Tokino Sora 7th anniversary goods, so please check them out!
私、ときのそらのニューシングル「おかえりなさい」が9月11日にリリースになります！
My, Tokino Sora's, new single "Okaerinasai" will be released on September 11!
TVアニメ「君の妻は感情がない」オープニング主題歌として現在応援中です！
It is currently airing as the opening theme song for the TV anime "My Wife Has No Emotion"!
本日解禁になりました「ラッキーセブンスホイッスル」もシングルに収録されます！
"Lucky Seventh Whistle," which was unveiled today, is also included in the single!
こちらは7周年記念ソングとして制作しました！
This was produced as a 7th anniversary song!
どちらもメモリアルな楽曲になっているのでいっぱい聞いてください！
Both are memorial songs, so please listen to them a lot!
次はAZKiちー！
Next is AZKi-chi!
AZKiメジャーデビューライブ「コワイロエントロピー」追加公演9月17日18日豊洲PITにて開催します！
We are holding additional performances for the AZKi Major Debut LIVE "Kowairo Entropy" on Sept 17-18 at Toyosu PIT!
ぜひよろしくお願いします！そして現在アルバム「Route F」が配信中発売中です！
Please look forward to it! And currently, the album "Route F" is available for streaming and sale!
こちらもよろしくお願いします！次はみこち！
Please check this out as well! Next is Mikochi!
2024年10月26日土曜日にさくらみこファーストソロライブ「flower fantasista!」開催決定です！
Sakura Miko's 1st solo live "flower fantasista!" is decided for Saturday, October 26, 2024!
二次先行受付がなんと明日23時59分までです！お見逃しなきように！
The second pre-order reception is until tomorrow at 23:59! Don't miss it!
2024年9月25日にファーストアルバム「flower rhapsody」が発売決定しております！
The 1st album "flower rhapsody" is scheduled for release on September 25, 2024!
各店舗にてまだまだ予約受付中です！よろしくね！
Pre-orders are still open at various stores! Thank you!
それではすいちゃん！
Now, Suichan!
星街すいせいライブツアー2024「Spectra of Nova」の情報が解禁されました！
Information for Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova" has been announced!
さいたまスーパーアリーナ、マリンメッセ福岡、サンパレスホテルホールで11月14日から12月28日でツアーが開催されます！
The tour will be held from Nov 14 to Dec 28 at Saitama Super Arena, Marine Messe Fukuoka, and Sun Palace Hotel Hall!
月チケの一次抽選も始まっているのでぜひみんな応募してね！詳細はツアー特設サイトを見てね！
Ticket pre-lottery has also started, so please apply! Check the tour special site for details!
では最後にロボ子！
Now lastly Roboco!
えっと私個人はライブで僕たちのチャンネル登録もぜひよろしくお願いします！
Um, as for me personally, please subscribe to our channel as well at the live!
そしてなんとですね...
And surprisingly...
いよいよ！
Finally!
9月5日から10月2日まで、
From September 5th to October 2nd,
極楽湯コラボも開催中です！
the Gokurakuyu collaboration is underway!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな僕たち0期生の湯に浸かりに来てください！
Come soak in the hot water with us 0th generation!
それでは、
And now,
これからも0期生を、よろしくねー！
please keep supporting the 0th generation!